[Music]
sound to me for your lip
Bob no one crosses me twice fixed you
good fix your Flint I settle my scores
shot in the heart and I'm to blame
seems more like a tactic to land their
pockets
but what do I know your company likes
making headlines
bless your heart
Farm it dead is a doornail busy work
time to get this rolling let's ride tell
the devil I said howdy Bullseye I'm the
queen around these parts that one's on
the house one shot huh
You'll Never Take Me Alive
Giddy Up wanna make it out of this do
what I say I would not recommend the
coffee here not my idea The Good Life
NASA spend some time in the clubhouse
riding ahead of the herd now sweat off
my brow right on the money I'll be
keeping the change now who's the better
shot
ah
[Music]
remember who's in charge traitors never
prosper
maybe next time sugar Angela's singing
with the angels now
not a rain cloud in sight is it Girl
Scout have a nice day I stick up from my
crew courtesy of the deadlock gang you
need to learn the rules don't waste my
time
right on schedule he's just fine thank
you for your concern too competent you
make that sound like a bad thing you'd
still be on a farm if it weren't for me
it was a Shay's Lounge
whoo
ah
payload's all mine let's move
playing around and get him off the point
payloads in my hands know your place
outclassed nice try honey never should
have let you get away from Treasure to
trash I'm taking the payload huh brought
a knife to a gunfight a royal disgrace
I'll quit your jibber jabber hell
doesn't freeze over that easily solved
our little rat problem they say the
Outlaws ghost still stalks those cursed
planes I already earned my stripes doors
taking a beating that door looks worse
for wear that door ain't looking so good
those monsters have done a number on our
door the reaper got what he had coming
monster down
oh wait what a stink bang down goes the
doctor
y'all can all calm down now I got the
Summoner yeah I killed the witch
thank me later come to the objective now
come over to the objective Off to the
Races giddy up let's get a move on keep
your distance
Mosey on over here enjoy the fireworks
short fuse boom knock down up and out I
like my space decided to make yourself
useful Color Me impressed you're a real
Sharpshooter didn't think you had the
stomach for it can about a show off
stop that robot
stop the robot come on let's get him
they want to fight huh let's give it to
him We're outnumbered they got us
outnumbered over there coming from down
below they got behind us they're right
in front of us
spotted them eyes on the bad guys enemy
Bastion left side enemy Bastion behind
us
something doesn't feel right capture the
objective
stay focused and let's bring home the
bacon keep your eyes on the prize tell
the objective time to put our heads down
and end this properly come on down to
objective town
someone stop that payload should be a
leave around here that'll open the
secret passage there ain't a prison
round that could keep me locked up now
get pulling cut into the chase didn't
feel like waiting around
nailed it I am hurt pretty badly I need
a doctor now damn they got me good get
me back in the fight coming from above
us they're on the left enemies on the
right
enemy Bastion on the right there's an
enemy Bastion coming for us it is hard
to find good help these days I guess
that's that
I'm with you ready out of my space you
just went boom
three two one
I'm on the objective come over if you
want to cut I think we're just about
done here what else
Revenge not feeling so good I need some
better help
get our flag back let's get that flag
back patched up that's better
you should join my crew okay put a price
on Good Help
enemy Bastion up ahead
much better
you follow they're coming from below
watch the left they're above us watch
all right they're coming straight at us
behind us ready to go I got you back is
taking out the trash
hahaha
it's a given time of year in three two
one taking the objective is my prize get
those swine off the objective drive
those goons off the payload I'm on the
point stop slacking off
don't let them move the payload do not
let them take the point someone's down
get them back on their feet we lost one
stop fooling around we're one shot stay
on your toes they're pounding on the
door get them off the door doors taking
damage come on guard that door don't
mind if I do all Gone With the Wind I'm
at the top of my game you're headed to
the bottom let's do this on it pull in
your horns mind your distance
step back this town just ain't big
enough
now to show them that I mean business I
ain't a quitter I am not ready to ride
into the sunset I know one thing
someone's gonna pay I'm about to pitch a
fit I don't take Conley to be a knock
down let's get back in the saddle you
won't get the best of me
stick it out and we take this home hold
out for a spell in this fight's hours
back from the bone Orchard oh hush push
that robot
shove that robot along she's at a switch
again knock her off the switch quick you
got a debt to pay hun and we aim to
collect she's at the switch do not let
her pull that switch she's on the switch
stop her can't hear myself think with
that radio blaring that sounds like the
Lord get a move on flag's mine are flags
out in the open you scared everybody get
ready bye see you later
fall back somebody get a Healer I think
this is going well
we got a good thing going let's not mess
it up it's not time to throw in the
towel yet enemy objectives taking fire
we need a Healer line them up
still too early to call it quits my
calls are red hot
they just don't stay down there is no
stopping me
ever seen one that wasn't Flags heading
back to base bringing the flag back to
base
they're using a shield generator
safe and sound oh our 14's behind us or
14's in front of us no Troopers coming
at us be right there ready for the
fireworks to begin you're welcome my
pleasure cutting it close not quite get
out of here back off pull out all
according to plan not bad at all keep it
up let's pick up the pace and end this
this is our last shot do whatever it
takes Last Chance everyone stay on the
robot My ultimate is ready Bob's ready
now you know what it's like to work with
the best
what'd you expect
I'm on fire
no Trooper over there they dropped our
flag let's get it back and force her up
ahead assassins disappeared or 14 on the
left watch that or 14 on the right or 14
coming at us on my way see you later
take a step back don't know when to quit
do they can't handle the heat stay out
of my way you should be quaking in your
boots
no hitting the sack we ain't done here
my fuse is lit
stand your ground this one's ours
enemies spotted enemy here there's one
here Bob cold as the wind down a
mountain pass
nasal Breeze just went through here you
feel that I'll pop the head right off
that Reaper there's a witch out there
well well if it ain't the Summoner get
her oh aren't you A big one an ugly to
boot it's the doctor blast him away it's
the witch let's get her quick home Home
on the Range
where the deer and the antelope play
where seldom is heard a discouraging
word in this guys are not cloudy all day
hey Bob come here
forgetting something gonna get that
please okay be that hard I'm waiting
clock's ticking dick the lead out I
ain't a quitter get in there thank you
kindly thanks you bet yep over here when
I catch Cassidy which I guarantee
y'all gonna see how much he regrets
Crossing me
step aside girls my Dynamite will burn
this door to the ground
I'm working on it all right just hold
your horses hurry up hurry up
get em over
I know you'll pay me back
Essence down
I got the Assassin nothing to worry
about enemy bastion's down incoming here
they come looks like it's up to me
destroy the objective press the attack I
know you're good for it woohoo
ha
payload's just sitting there get it
moving better be a good excuse for this
hold up now to put a stop to her seems
junkenstein wasn't the only inventive
one come out where I can see you I know
you're here defend our flag need someone
to babysit the flag any takers thank you
thanks just getting started you haven't
seen anything yet don't let up
Eradicator right in front of us best way
to win is to rig the game let's clear
this out I'm on the attack attacking
quit dogling and get a move on that was
an accident
stop that barricade in its tracks the
enemy's starting to move their barricade
we're in charge around here
we are in the lead that's all it takes
that's rich
behind you get in and snatch their flag
let's take that flag get on the
objective we're taking that objective I
owe you one get out of there damn oh
come on
laughs
[Laughter]
eradicators behind us Eradicator
incoming Eradicator on our right
Eradicator on the left watch out for
those slicers slicers coming in this is
a stick up
you owe me one focus on the heavy and
he's dead
somebody fetch my butler yes
Hallelujah best not leave this dead
unpaid does anyone care about moving the
payload hands off my merchandise they're
gaining on us stop them in their tracks
keep it moving we can't let them catch
up their barricade is pushing up get in
their way the barricades moving along
the robots pushing our barricade the
barricade's moving keep up I'll get in
the pool when I am good and ready
Dead Ahead Tire coming down the middle
shock Tire straight in front of us bust
down that door clear a path Cassidy's
down could leave him that way Cassidy's
down to no one's surprise count Em Up
get that doorway clear they don't call
me an outlaw for nothing they never
learn
better get digging Bob push over I'm the
last one you'll ever cross
you believe it damn some days I impress
myself yay
think I'm scared of you just cause
you're glowing bad ninja down red you
like the morning paper that shot would
make bars proud I can shoot the spines
off a cactus a mile away our blessed
rifles accurate at range get on over
here Brad's gone she's a tricky one her
Butler's back for Revenge
speak for yourself this experiment of
hers is downright unnatural drop that
now or I'll give you something to wail
about like shooting zombies under the
full moon
spotted The Shield generator knocked out
their Shield generator you can all just
take it easy get our flag back drop the
flag
find that teleporter
now that gets the blood pumping move the
objective good shooting Bob doors locked
won't get to the castle without a key
Ash here I'm not afraid to get my hands
dirty I can always count on you Bob dang
it Bob everybody come over here get over
here defend the objective we need to
defend the objective
laughs
I needed that Detonator right in front
of us
detonators behind us Detonator coming in
detonators on the left
enforcers down Bob get out of there get
in there Bob Bob
then
don't all volunteer at once now read you
like a book Cole
well would you look at the time no
raining over my desert atta boy Bob step
it up Bob enough Bob Bob I have had it
with you too bad you can't be angry and
smart at the same time
Bob do something thanks Bob I could use
some armor I'll take some armor if you
have it everybody get down take cover oh
just what I needed somebody get him back
up
somebody get them back up
someone get her back up someone get it
back up thank you ah
lost the flag damn it now Trooper down
they have our flag
detonator's on our right
snipers having a field day can we do
something about that sniper I'm an Easy
Rider you wanna try me we have an
understanding take out the target oh get
out of my way thanks for standing still
Cole reckon I know another way through
let's get to the dungeon we have a lot
in common Renegade both of us are on the
Run canis I imagine you've accumulated
quite a few Treasures over the years run
into any thieves where's the fun in that
Vikings never met me
you owe me for this you ain't dying
until I kill you this one's mine gotcha
I'll take that give me that got one
Dynamite out
she's gonna blow hey catch I enjoy a
good roast out with a bang never said
it'd be pretty understood I got you loud
and clear watch here heads up watch out
understood I gotcha I'm hurt over here
not again just thawing you out
that is not how we drew it up
score one for us
enemy turrets down enemy teleporters
destroyed enemy sniper get your head
down assassins Coming For You focus on
that assassin take out the Assassin
watch out for that assassin try and keep
it together get in there go objective
eliminated we're almost there we need to
group up Follow My Lead defend the
objective once or twice
I steer clear trouble like him this
place looks just as bad as the last time
I passed through
unless that's an accusation stop wasting
my time stay away from that thing unless
you want to be in a world of hurt I bet
these zomnics have something to do with
the lord of the castle and Dr
junkenstein No Doubt wouldn't be the
first time he clawed his way out of the
grave and maybe I made a Town's gold
disappear happy the closed-minded folks
out west don't take kindly to conjurers
don't reckon you can see if we survive
the night
huh of course not you're not getting out
of this that easily somebody get me some
healing I need healing stop the payload
just showing you how it's done looks
nice and quiet from up here
slicers destroyed it never gets fast
enough for me do you trust me let's sit
up here get them off that robot and
we'll end this if we push them off the
robot it's over let's put an end to this
the enemy took our lead now get back in
there I'm a rebel mind your manners it's
all about life's Little Pleasures here
it comes fire in the hole smoke them out
of there get ready for Bob my ultimate's
charged get ready let's push the payload
back let's move the payload out let's
get our payload moving
[Music]
that was not the plan detonators
destroyed
that's what you get the girl who has
everything push forward enemy Snapper
keep your eyes open they're further
along than we are stop them we're
falling behind the robot is coming with
us let's go took control of the robot
move out this robot's all mine let's
move honey when a mad scientist has to
buy your corpses you say no if I'm not
mistaken you knew that crackpot doctor
I've been looking for a medic and a
marksman to join my operation didn't
expect to find both in one hey canis
what do you think about when you're
looking down that scope we've killed a
whole mess of them and they just keep
coming do my eyes to save me or are you
wearing skates
nice skates very cute you gonna swap
those out before we get to the gun fight
thanks but I already have a bodyguard is
that a costume or are you just ugly not
much door left just a couple of planks
door's taking so much damage I can't
believe it's still standing doors Two
flicks of a donkey's tail from going
down that door's just about breached
tire from the left
somebody please kill that witch
Monster's Still Standing knock him down
there's a tire on the left left side
shock Tire coming in hot watch your
right it's on the right smash it Tire on
the right son of a somebody kill that
Reaper how is the doctor still alive
take him down
slay the Summoner quick now can't say I
do this way over here oh Bob
I'll tell him you said hello help me
pick this up damn I dropped it I'm dying
to see how you botched this one Cassidy
I'm in charge don't forget that
me
shows over I ain't a snitch but let's
just say those corn dogs are gone for
good that he does what the hell do you
give Bob all that Firepower your parents
ever pester you about going back to the
family business
she's not gonna miss if you come around
again where's my backup let's work
together this time where is everybody
I'll only ask one more time Cassidy
where'd you leave my bike yeah and those
who seek my wrath tend to find it this
place just ain't the same since that son
of a gun ran away with my bike look at
all these Good Samaritans what are we
doing here Bob I think they have a
teleporter assassins over here
assassin's on me do you need me to
repeat myself let me handle it just
point me in the right direction I get
the idea I'm going in we're doing this
my way we've almost got it nope nah bite
me wouldn't be enough up there to blow
your nose
blew him out of the water I'll take some
Shields spare me some Shields Bob's not
ready yet or 14 destroyed Life is a
Highway are you serious sorry about that
defending over here no over here I'm
right here not my first rodeo certainly
not my last
I'll go on the straight and narrow when
hell freezes over Stone Anthony says you
still owe him 500 for that weekend in
Tucson seems to think you're gonna shoot
him dead if he does how do you even live
Bob's taking a breather My ultimate is
charging
I took care of The Eradicator we need to
prioritize the heavy assault get on the
heavy careful it was worth it
not a chance no one likes a Squealer
Bullseye my mistake I'm going on defense
we're right at their Knicks keep up the
pressure we're almost there get a move
on we can take the lead from here keep
pushing huh
ha Castle should be up this way that
would be Mighty appreciated it's serving
me just fine thanks
don't trust anyone oh and uh never miss
an opportunity to wash your socks
hey now I prefer self-employed wealth
requisitioner am I supposed to be
thankful for that that's a lot of armor
though I guess you are a pretty big
Target
their rifle's a fine piece of work looks
a little unwieldy though yeah our
teammates wearing skates to a gun fight
laughs Rodeo only good days
how y'all doing
tell me you don't mean Cassidy they say
you're a good shot
hope you don't mind that I'm better head
to the objective get over to the
Waypoint object is close let's hurry
let's get this show on the road better
get paid after all this
I don't like having my time wasted
saddle up we got work to do time to
settle who's the best shot and I was
trained by the West how sweet of them I
hear you can smuggle just about anything
through those skyways this is a hearty
bunch of Outlaws just need something to
steal I wouldn't mind stealing a
spaceship you hear what they make
satellites out of these days if I find
even a scratch on it Bob's gonna use you
for target practice can you build me a
bike money's no object
all right
how about a new chassis for Bob oh hell
the law is here hey howdy how's it going
howdy I don't know I ain't a necromancer
you need a better hobby maybe one that
won't lead to your untimely demise we
need to take out that turret enemy
turret up ahead
spotted their teleporter we're playing
by my rules my name's Ash we're playing
by my rules now get to the objective
good I'll kick some up for you good
thing your brains aren't made of
dynamite we may have different
definitions
Bob Bob's almost ready my ultimate is
almost ready follow the rules and we
won't have a problem you still have any
contacts with los Muertos
help me need a little help here we hunt
foxes where I come from
same thing I'm partial to scorpions a
wanted man on the run I've known a few
of you
it's a good thing I'm heartless
burn it all down
I run this show
hello
hey been a while I'd offer you money but
I don't think that's what you're after
from what I can tell you and I are
sympatico on how we like things run
they're all over here what's your
language no arguments here absolutely I
hate to be interrupted reckon that's
true good thing I have both they took
the robot we need to get that robot back
oh come on we let them take the robot
I'm watching over here I'll cover this
area fixing my sights over here
I can't believe we lost such valuable
cargo you would have fetched to find
some considering that you have to deal
with coal I'd say it's really your loss
you need a dose of reality Little Miss
Sunshine till the sun gets in your eyes
every good storm needs some wind I'm
feeling divine